http://www.dac.com/content/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
ConferenceCall for ContributionsAbout DACUnder 40 AwardWomen in Technology @ DACStudents & ScholarshipsCommitteesConference SponsorsA Tribute to Pat PistilliConference ArchiveFuture SitesExhibitionExhibit @ DAC2021 Floor Plan & Exhibitor ListDesign Infrastructure AlleyRISC-V PavilionSEMICON WestFor ExhibitorsAttendWhy Attend DAC?Moscone Center WestTravel VISASister ConferencesMedia CenterDAC Press ReleasesDAC in the NewsDAC Logos & BrandDAC BlogDACtv
Privacy Policy
Design Automation Conference is highly sensitive to the privacy interests of consumers and believes that the protection of those interests is one of its most significant responsibilities. In acknowledgment of its obligations; DAC has adopted the following Privacy Policy applicable to information about consumers that it acquires in the course of its business.ACM Privacy PolicyIEEE Privacy Policy
1. Acquisition of Information. We do not acquire any more information about consumers than is required by law or is otherwise necessary to provide a high level of service efficiently and securely.2. Our Employees and Privacy. We train all of our employees about the importance of privacy. We give access to information about consumers only to those employees who require it to perform their jobs.3. Security Measures. We make access to privacy-sensitive information subject to rigorous procedural and technological controls, consistent with legal requirements and the demands of customer service.4. Disclosure to Third Parties. We will provide individually identifiable information about consumers to third parties only if we are compelled to do so by order of a duly-empowered governmental authority, we have the express permission of the consumer, or it is necessary to process transactions and provide our services.5. Privacy and Our Business Partners. When we make our technology or services available to business partners, we will not share with them any more consumer information than is necessary, and we will make every reasonable effort to assure, by contract or otherwise, that they use our technology and services in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy.
DAC 58July 11-15, 2021San FranciscoCall for Contributions
Exhibit at DACDAC is the premier conference devoted to the design and automation of  electronic systems (EDA), embedded systems and software (ESS), and  intellectual property (IP).Become an Exhibitor
DAC BlogKeep up to date with the 58th Design Automation Conference.Stay Connected
